늦었잖아.
지루해 죽을 뻔했어.
You're late.
And we're dying.
오, 짜증나.
"Shot me": 실망했다, 짜증나게 했다 정도의 의미
여기서는 '총에 맞은 듯한 포즈'를 취하며 중의적으로 표현
Oh, someone shoot me.
지난 밤에 또 음주파티라도 하셨나?
Girls' night again last night?
이번엔 또 뭐야? 어디 보자.
What was it this time?
Let me guess.
어. 베르무트.
"베르무트(Vermouth)": 술의 한 종류
Ugh. Vermouth.
음.
Mm.
이봐, 그 술은 취하려고 마시는 그런 게 아니라고.
You know, that stuff's
not supposed to be
그건 식전주라고.
guzzled-- it's an ap챕ritif.
뭐?
A what?
식.전.주.
An ap챕ritif.
식사 전에 마시는 식욕 돋워주는 알콜음료.
Alcoholic beverage
served before the meal
to stimulate the appetite.
훔친 야채 상자 옮기는 놈 주제에 별 소릴 다하는군.
Pretty fancy talk
for a guy carrying
a box of
stolen pickles.
훔친 거 아냐.
These are not stolen.
이 배달물품들은 내 사촌이 운영하던, 음,
The distributor
over-ordered,
my cousin did some, uh,
유능한 물품관리지.
creative inventory management.
야채 도둑 사촌이 당신을 곤란하게 만들겠군.
Pickle thief cousin
is going to get you
into trouble.
그냥 야채일 뿐이야.
They're just
pickles.
어떻게 하면 야채따위가 날 곤란하게 할 수 있겠어?
Tell me how some pickles
are gonna get me in trouble.
세상에.
My God.
♪ NCIS 12시즌 11화 ♪ "Check"
2015년 1월 6일 방송분
NCIS 12x11
Check
Original Air Date on January 6, 2015
영문자막 elderman / 한글번역 꺄~♡오즈
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ ♪
좋은 아침.
Morning.
오, 안녕.
안녕.
Oh, morning.
Morning.
최근에 캣 비디오 봤어?
"캣 비디오(cat video)": 흥미 위주의 짧은 동영상
See any good cat videos lately?
나만 모르는 게 뭐 있어?
Did I miss something?
아니요, 그냥 하는 말이에요.
No, just making small talk.
아.
Ah.
근데, 그거 새 셔츠인가요?
Hey, is that a new shirt?
되게 하얗네요.
It's really white.
새 거는 아니고. 새해부턴 옷장에서 하얀 것을 따로 두려고 결심했...
No. I actually made
a New Year's resolution
to separate my whites from my col...
이거 찾아?
You looking for this?
팀 맥기가 작성한 "새해 결심"?
"New Year's Resolutions"
by Tim McGee?
내 책상을 뒤졌나요?
You went into my desk?
이거 봐봐. "4번, 책상을 잠근다."
Look at that.
"Number four, lock my desk."
벌써 실패했구만.
You've already failed.
됐어요, 내놔요.
All right, give me that.
세상에 누가 그런 걸 새해 결심으로 해요,
Who makes a New Year's
resolution to stop watching
캣 비디오 그만 보기.
cat videos?
외로운 연방요원.
A lonely federal agent
그에게는 고양이가 필요한 걸지도.
who may be in need of a cat.
선배 새해 결심은 뭔데요, 응?
What are your
New Year's resolutions, huh?
제 걸 가졌으니, 선배 것도 보여줘요.
You got to see mine.
Show me yours.
커피 그만 마시기.
He stopped drinking coffee.
아니, 아닌데.
No, I did not.
하지만 그것도 괜찮긴 하네.
Although that
would be a good one.
뭐요? 아니, 아녜요. 깁스 요원님 얘기에요.
What? No, no, not
you. Agent Gibbs.
뭐? 깁스는 새해 결심 같은 거 안 써.
What? Gibbs doesn't make
New Year's resolutions.
새 해 결심은 아니죠. 말러드 박사님께 하시는 얘길 엿들었어요.
It's not a resolution.
I overheard him
talking to Dr. Mallard.
깁스 요원님이 검진을 받아야하고, 주치의가 카페인을 피하랬어요.
Gibbs is going in for a
checkup and his doctor
told him to avoid
caffeine for
72시간 동안요.
72 hours.
어, 그건... 곤란하네요.
Mm-mm, that seems... unwise.
그건 그를 죽일지도 몰라.
더 나쁠지도.
That could kill him.
Or worse.
그, 그분은 평소 적절히 카페인을 섭취할 때도 충분히 무섭다구요.
T-The guy-guy's scary enough
when he's properly medicated.
카페인 없는 그분은 상상이 안 가요.
Can't imagine what he'll be like
with caffeine withdrawal.
상상이 가는 건...
Can only imagine
킹콩의 바나나조차 확 빼앗는(?) 모습이네요.
※매우 화난 모습 정도일까요?
someone taking away
King Kong's bananas.
돌아서지 않을 겁니다.
I'm not going
to turn around.
좋은 생각이야.
Good idea.
멋진 비유였어, 짐.
That's a good analogy, Jim.
고맙군요.
Thank you.
최고는 아니었어요, 보스.
It wasn't the greatest, boss.
시체 5구가 발견됐다.
Got five bodies.
가지.
Let's go.
이건...
This is...
시체가 너무 많군요.
a lot of dead bodies.
무슨 일이 있었던 걸까요?
What do you think happened?
자네가 말해보지.
You tell me.
음...
Uh...
제가 보기에는 서로가 서로를 쏜 것 같아요.
Looks like they all
shot each other.
무승부네요.
"Mexican standoff": 무승부(도박 용어)
Some kind of Mexican standoff.
흥미롭구만.
Interestingly enough,
그 용어는 호주인들에게서 기원했다고 하지.
that term
is of Australian origin.
최소한, 캠브리지 사전에 따르면 말이지.
At least, according
to the Cambridge
Advanced Learner's
Dictionary.
뭐, 확실한 건지는 나도 모르겠지만 말야.
Though it's unattributed,
so I have my doubts.
음, 그렇군요.
Mm, good to know.
어디서부터 시작하죠?
Where should we start?
여기. 이 대령.
Right here. The captain.
핸노버 대령, 43세.
Captain Sharon Hanover, 43.
펜타곤의 사무직열인데요,
A desk jockey
at the Pentagon who
명백히 총격전에 참여한 것 같죠?
apparently also likes
to get into gunfights?
운반할 것들을 좀 가져오지.
Let's get some bags.
보스, 가게주인과 얘기해 봤습니다.
McGEE:
Boss, spoke with the owner.
시체들 전부 여기 직원이 아니랍니다.
None of the bodies
are employees.
아는 얼굴은?
없대요, 하지만 좀 불안해 보이더군요.
Did he recognize anybody?
No, but he's
acting a little
squirrelly.
아무것도 모르오.
I don't know nothing.
네, 그렇게 말씀하셨죠.
그럼 이제 끝난 거요?
Yeah, you said that.
So we're done here?
아뇨.
No.
계속해서 모른다고만 하셨는데요,
Every time you say
you don't know nothing,
그건 뭔가 알고 있단 것처럼 들리는군요.
it makes me think
you know something.
그렇죠, 그건 진짜 야채...
Yeah, it's a real
엘리스.
pickle.
Alice.
더 말해줄 것 있습니까?
There something
you want to tell us?
없소.
No.
당신이 그 야채에 대해 말하지 않으면, 내가 할거야.
If you don't tell him
about the pickles, I will.
야채가 무슨 소리죠?
What's the deal
with the pickles?
안됩니다, 들어가실 수 없어요.
No, ma'am, you can't
walk up through here.
들어가야만 한다고요.
아뇨, 아뇨, 안됩니다.
I just have to go inside.
No, no, no, no,
안되요, 안돼. 노란 줄 보이시죠?
no, no. You see
the yellow line?
노란 줄 넘어가시면 안됩니다.
넘어가면요, 체포라도 할 건가요?
You can't cross the yellow line.
What are you gonna to do, arrest me?
곧바로 돌아오도록 하지.
I'll be right back.
우, 야채에서 잠시 중단.
Ooh. Hold the pickle.
내가 누군지 알고 이러는 거죠?
And you have no idea who I am,
도가 지나치군요, 총 찬 양반.
you overgrown,
armed Smurf.
깁스 요원을 만나야 한다고요, 지금 바로.
I need to see agent Gibbs
and I need to see him now.
기다리셔야 합니다.
You're gonna have to wait.
좋아요, 경찰관 9-60,
All right, Officer 9-60,
매우 고맙군요, 윌슨.
thank you very much,
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
워워워, 무슨 일이지?
Mr. Wilson.
What's going on?
이 여성분 아시나요?
내 전부인.
You know this woman?
My ex-wife.
안녕, 제이.
Hello, J.
그리고 저분은요?
And that one?
또 다른...
Also...
내 전부인.
my ex-wife.
오, 이이 좀 봐. 도망가지도 지리지도 못하고 어쩔 줄 몰라하는데.
Aw, look at him.
He didn't know whether
난 재밌는데.
to run or wet himself.
I like it.
두려워하는 게 섹시하네.
Fear is sexy.
서로 아는 사이야?
You two know each other?
주의.
문어발 여사가 떴음.
Heads up. Lady Octopus sighting.
좋아, 도망가진 않네.
Well, he's not running.
아랫도리가 깨끗해야할텐데.
Hope he has a clean
pair of underwear.
나랑 결혼했을 때도 이이 아랫도리가 깨끗하진 않았어.
He didn't wear underwear
when we were married.
저는...
I'm...
가봐야겠군요.
gonna go someplace else.
수고하시죠.
Works for me.
여긴 무슨 일들일까요?
What's she doing here?
그리고 같이 있는 건 누구예요, 토니 선배?
2번.
- And who is she with?
- Number two.
부인 2번.
That's wife number two.
내 눈이 틀림없다면 말이지.
We have a visual
confirmation.
뭐, 제쓰로, 무슨 말이든 해보지,
Well, Jethro,
you gonna say anything
아니면 혀가 굳어버린 거야?
or did your tongue
finally shrivel up and die?
서로 아는 사이야?
You two know each other?
뭐, 당신이랑 투바이스만 전배우자끼리 친구가 될 수 있을까봐?
What, are you and Tobias
the only two exes
that get to be friends?
우린 감성적인 난장인 지지자 모임(?)에서 만났지.
We met at an emotional dwarf
support group.
그거 좋네, 맘에 들어.
고마워.
- That's a good one, I like that.
- : Thanks.
여기서 뭐하는 건데?
What are you doing here?
내가 데려왔어. 당신들은 대화가 필요해.
I brought her.
You two need to talk.
그리고 우리도 당신이 관심 없다는 거 알아.
And we all know that's not
something you're interested in.
잘 아는군.
Got that right.
그래서 내가 제안했는데...
So I suggested that we...
사건현장에서 날 덮치면, 내가 도망 못 갈 것이다?
Ambush me at a crime scene
so I can't get away?
다시 일 시작.
Get back to work.
죄송합니다만, 보스, 저, 저희가 그냥 이 시간을...
Sorry, boss, we-we were just
taking these cases back to...
네 "최후"의 휴식?
Your final resting place?
저기 뭐 있네.
There's a thing up there.
지금은 대화 못 해.
I can't talk right now.
그럼 기다릴게.
그것도 안돼.
- Then I'll wait.
- That's not gonna work.
좋아, 알았다구, 타협하자.
Okay, okay, let's compromise.
우리는 NCIS 사무실에 가 있을게, 여기 일 마치고 만나자.
We'll got back to NCIS and meet
you there once you're done here.
내게 선택권이 있나?
뭐, 경우에 따라서는...
Do I have a choice?
Well, that depends--
대안으로 6개월 정도 동안 조사당하며 지낼 수도 있지.
how do you feel
about spending the next
six months being audited?
나한테서 말야.
By me.
피해자 1번, 샘슨 딜가도 하사.
Victim number one, Staff
Sergeant Samson Delgado.
콴티코에서 전투 훈련 교관입니다.
근육 덩어리라고 비꼬는 거겠죠?
Teaches combat training
at Quantico.
체력단련, 구보, 체력단련...
Likes pumping iron,
hiking,
and pumping iron.
피해자 2번...
Victim number two--
고급하사관 보 로딘.
Chief Petty Officer
Beau Lordin.
아프가니스탄에서 돌아온 지 얼마 안되었고요,
Just got back
from Afghanistan,
거기서 훈장을 받았습니다.
where he received
a commendation
지뢰로부터 2명의 지역주민을 구했거든요.
for saving two locals
from a land mine.
이크.
Yeesh.
아, 보시면 안되는 걸 보셨네요, 보스.
Uh, you weren't
supposed to see that, boss.
하지만, 어, 다 보셨으니까,
But, uh, now that you did,
좀 궁금하네요...
we were
just wondering...
부인 2번...
Wife number two--
보스가 침대에 다른 남자랑 있는 걸 잡은 그녀죠?
she's the one you caught
in bed with the other guy?
전 궁금하지 않습니다.
I wasn't wondering that.
아, 저, 저도요.
Uh, me, neither.
그럼 저만 그랬나 보네요. 넘어가죠.
It was just me, then.
Moving on.
5명 피해자 모두 경력이 대단하더군요.
All five victims
have stellar records.
범죄기록도 조사된 게 없구요.
Nothing to indicate
any criminal activity.
특이한 점은?
Anything in common?
아, 네, 모두들 지난 주에 보고 의무를 어겼어요.
Uh, yes, they all failed
to report for duty last week.
뭔가 있더군요, 보스, 하지만 뭔지는 잘 모르겠습니다.
There's something else,
boss, but I'm not
quite sure what
to make of it.
그들 모두 세금납부에 늦었어요.
They're all late
paying their taxes.
케이먼에 있는 작은 은행에 충분한 벌금을 지불했구요.
They've paid enough
late fees to buy a small bank
그게 다예요..
in the Caymans.
It could be nothing.
(지금은) 여기까집니다. 하지만 계속 캐 보죠.
Run it down.
But we're gonna run it down.
어떻게 피해자들이 그 식당에서 마지막 만찬을 하게 되었는지 알아내도록.
Find out how our victims
ended up in that diner.
좋아.
Okay.
계속해볼까?
What did we learn?
피해자들이 어떻게 그 마지막 만찬을 했는지는 모르겠지만,
I can't tell you how our victims
ended up in the diner,
거기서 무슨 일이 있었던 건지 알 방도는 있죠.
but do I have
a good idea of
what happened once
they got there.
남자 피해자들은 여자 피해자를 둘러싸고 있었어요.
Our male victims
surrounded our female victim.
그녀가 여기에요.
She was here.
그녀가 먼저 총을 쐈어요.
She got off the first shot.
남자 피해자 1번은 총을 쏴보지도 못했죠.
Male number one never
even fired his weapon.
핸노버 대령은 직후에 총을 맞았어요.
Captain Hanover took on
heavy fire after that.
어깨에 한 방, 팔에 한 방.
One to the shoulder,
one to the arm.
그녀는 그래도 계속 총을 쐈고, 남자 피해자 2, 3번이 맞았죠.
She kept firing, took out male
number two
and male number three.
그 다음 그녀가 한쪽 무릎을 끓고,
Then she dropped to one knee,
세 방을 더 쐈고, 남자 피해자 4번이 다 맞았어요.
fired three more shots,
took out male number four.
그리고 그녀는 피를 너무 많이 흘렸죠.
And by then she had
lost too much blood.
그래서 무승부가 된 거군.
It wasn't a Mexican standoff.
아뇨, 4:1이잖아요.
No. It was four against one.
핸노버가 최악의 상황에서도 잘 싸웠다는 거군.
그렇죠, 제 말은...
Hanover put up a hell of a fight.
Yeah. I mean,
그녀는 무기 사용 경험이 거의 없는 사무직 군인이었다는 거에요.
for a desk jockey with very
little weapons experience.
그러니까, 모피우스가 더티 헨리를 그녀의 뇌에 다운로드하거나, 아니면
"모피우스(Morpheus)": 그리스 신화, 잠과 꿈의 신
"더티 해리(Dirty Henry)" 스티븐 시갈 주연의 동명 영화의 주인공
I mean, unless Morpheus
had just downloaded
Dirty Harry into her
brain. Or else she's
그녀가 핸노버처럼 생긴 다른 사람이 아니라면요.
이거 좀 드실래요?
not who she seems. Do
you want some of this?
그래.
Yeah.
어, 총기는?
Uh, ballistics?
음, 시리얼 넘버는 다 지워져 있었어요.
Um, all the serial numbers
were ground down,
그리고 총기 데이터베이스와 맞는 게 없었어요.
and I didn't get any hits
on the ballistics databases,
하지만 흥미로운 걸 발견했죠.
but I did find
something interesting
피해자들의 달력에서요.
in our victims' calendars.
모두 약속이 있더군요.
They all had appointments
어떤 세금 회계 회사와 예약되어 있었어요.
on the books
with a tax-consulting firm
그들이 사라진 바로 그 주에요.
the weekend they disappeared.
모두 같은 회사예요, 깁스.
The same firm, Gibbs.
주소는?
Got an address?
아뇨, 이름만 있어요.
No. Just a name.
'우리가 당신의 미납세금을 가지고 있다(We Got Your Back Taxes)'.
We Got Your Back Taxes.
검색해봤지만, 나오는 게 없었어요.
I ran a search,
but nothing came up.
뭐, 계속 찾고 있구요.
Well, keep looking.
뭔가 찾으면 연락 줘.
Call me if you
find something.
집으로 가야겠어.
I'll be at home.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠시만요.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
전부인 2번?
Ex-wife number two?
제 생각엔 그분이 여기 깁스 보러 오는 중인 거 같은데요.
I thought she was coming here
to see you.
그래, 오고 있지.
Yeah, she's coming.
그게 내가 집으로 가는 이유야.
That's why I'm going home.
뭐라도 찾았나, 맥기?
What do you got, McGee?
네, 토니가 피해자 중 한 명의 사무실 책상에서 신용카드를 찾았어요.
Well, Tony found a business card
in one
of the victim's office desk.
거기에 우리가 찾던 세금 컨설턴트 회사 주소가 있었구요,
It has the address
of our missing tax consultants,
하지만 전부 브릿지워터 주소로 되어 있더라구요.
but it's all the way
in Bridgewater.
그럼 빨리 착수해.
Then we start early.
새벽에 나 데리러 오고.
Pick me up at dawn.
저, 7시로 해도 될까요?
Actually, can we make it 7:00?
다이엔이 국세청(IRS)에 근무해서,
Since Diane works at the IRS,
그녀가 우리 피해자의 세금 기록을 확인해주겠다고 했거든요.
she offered to pull
our victims' tax records.
내일쯤 그 자료가 도착한다고 하더군요.
She's dropping them off
tomorrow.
다이엔?
네.
Diane?
McGEE: Yeah.
그녀가, 어, (보스가 사무실을) 떠난 직후에 전부인 2번 분과 함께 오셨거든요.
She, uh, came in with ex-wife
number two after you left.
아시죠, 보스, 그녀가 보스가 없는 걸 알고 미쳐 날뛰었다구요.
I got to say, boss, she was
crazy mad you were gone.
맥기, 그건 그녀가 미쳐 있기 때문이야.
McGee, it's because
she is crazy.
내가 미쳐? 말도 안되는 소리로군.
I'm crazy? Says the guy
who cuts his toenails
with a tin snip.
당신이 거짓말 했잖아!
You lied to me!
NCIS 사무실에서 보기로 약속 했잖아!
You promised to meet
me back at NCIS!
난 약속한단 말 한 적 없는데.
오, 아니, 아니.
I didn't hear the word "promise."
Oh, no, no.
안돼. 이번에는 얼버무릴 수 없어, 당신...
No. You are not weaseling
out of this this time, you...
당신...
You...
...이 옳아.
are right.
확실히, 약속이란 말은 하지 않았지.
Technically, you didn't
use the word "promise."
하지만 난 여기 왔고, 우린 얘길 좀 해야 해.
But I'm here now,
and we need to talk.
하기 싫은데.
I don't need to talk.
해야 해.
I do.
한 잔 할래?
Want a drink?
나, 난 괜찮아.
I-I don't
이젠 술 안 마셔.
drink anymore.
사실 그게 내가 여기 온 이유야.
That's actually why I'm here.
술 안 마시기 위해서?
To not drink?
난...
I...
바닥을 쳤었어...
bottomed out...
한 1년 전쯤에.
about a year ago.
친구 하나가 날 시설에 집어넣었지.
A friend got me
into the program.
그게 내 삶을 구했지.
It saved my life.
그리고 이제, 난 당신과의 일을 개선해야하는 그 부분에 머물러 있어.
And now, I'm at the part
where you make amends.
어, 당신의 경우에는, 어디서 시작해야할지...
미안해.
Which, in your case,
starts with... I'm sorry.
아, 오래전 이야기군.
Oh. Ancient history.
당신이 딴 남자와 침대에 있는 내 방에 들어왔었지.
You walked in on me in
bed with another man.
(그 잘못이 무효가 될) 공소시효가 있다고는 생각 안 해.
I don't think there's a
statute of limitations.
그게 어떨지 상상도 안 가.
I can't imagine what
that must have been like.
미안해, 제이.
I am so sorry, J.
됐어.
Okay.
됐다고?
Okay?
그래. 됐어.
Yeah. Okay.
이게 내가 당신을 좋아하는 이유지.
It's why I always liked you.
말수가 적지만, 항상 옳은 말만 하는 남자.
A man of few words, but
always the right ones.
이제 괜찮은 거야?
You doing all right now?
응, 더 이상 좋을 수 없지.
Yeah, better than all right.
당신은?
You?
어. 그래, 그렇지. 어, 나도.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Oh, same.
편두통이 좀 있지만.
Aside from a killer headache.
뭐, 난 항상 그걸 어떻게 고치는지 알았었지.
Well, I always knew
how to fix those.
이리와봐.
Come here.
그건... 이리와.
It's... Come here.
좋군.
Man.
이 손가락 느낌 기억나.
I remember those fingers.
흠.
Hmm.
보스?
Boss?
척키, 뭐가 그렇게 오래 걸려?
Chuckie, what's taking so long?
보스?
왜 이렇게 오래 걸리냐니...?
- Boss?
- How long does it take to...?
성스런 독립기념일의 엿 같은!
Holy Fourth of July
weenie roast!
내가 대체 뭘 보고 있는거야?!
What the hell am I looking at?!
오우!
Whoa!
워우!
이건 그런 게 아냐.
This is not what
it looks like.
그런 게 뭔데?
What does it look like?
우린 대화를 나누다, 그러다 잠들었어.
We were up talking,
and we fell asleep.
바로 지금까지 서로 껴안고 말이지, 흥?
Just wore yourselves
right out, huh?
저는 차에 가 있겠습니다.
I'm gonna go wait
in the car.
넌 이이와 관계를 개선하려던 거였지,
그와 역사를 만들려던 게 아니었잖아!
You are supposed
to be making amends,
not making his year!
안했어! 아니라고! 우엑!
I didn't! I wouldn't! Yuck!
우엑?
Yuck?
그건 무슨 의미로 낸 소리야?
What's that supposed to mean?
5시간 전에, 당신은 쉬지 않고 내 그걸 문질러 줬...
Five hours ago, you
couldn't wait to rub my...
오, 저기 봐요. 고양이네요.
Oh, look. It's a cat.
바깥에요. 저는 나가서 고양이 도와줘야겠네요.
Outside. I'm gonna go help it.
맥기, 잠깐! 이 사람은 여기서 뭐하는 거야?
McGee, stop!
What is she doing here?
말 돌리지 마요.
Don't try to change the subject.
명령했잖아.
That's an order.
그녀가 피해자들의 세금 기록에서 뭔가 발견했습니다.
She found something
in our victim's tax records.
그녀 스스로 얘기하길 원해서요.
Wanted to tell you herself.
So tell me.
[동시에] 그럼 말해.
So tell him.
오, 그렇게 쉽게 당신들 둘을 넘어가게 놔둘 것 같아?
Oh, you think I'm gonna
let the two of you
off the hook that easy?
내 생각엔, 내게는 왜 사랑하는 사람을 잃었는지 알고 싶어하는 다섯 가족들이 있는 것 같은데.
I think
I got five families members
who want to know
why their loved ones are dead.
그리고 당신은 그 시간을 낭비하고 있고.
And you're
wasting time.
나중에 계속하죠.
To be continued.
당신 둘 다.
Both of you.
피해자들의 세금 서류를 살펴봤어요.
I was looking through
your victims' tax filings,
열람기록에 뭔가 있더군요.
and I noticed something
in the log.
누군가 외부의 사람이 그들의 기록을 벌써 살폈어요.
Someone has already viewed them
from outside the agency.
국세청(IRS)이 해킹당했었습니다.
McGEE:
The IRS was hacked.
누군가 그들의 파일을 조사했습니다.
Somebody was
combing through their files
해군 소속 중에 세금을 늦게 낸 게 누군지 알아내기 위해서요.
to find Navy sailors who were
late paying their taxes.
무슨 의도인지 모르겠어요.
I have no idea what it means.
하지만, 다행하게도, 당신이라면 답을 찾을 수 있겠죠.
But, hopefully, you can find
some answers at that tax office.
우흐! 너... 나쁜 년...
Ugh! You-- hot lips--
가자. 볼 일 다 봤겠지.
let's go. You're done.
오, 음, 사실, 줄 게 있었어요.
Oh, uh, actually, there's
something else.
그, 그거면 의미가 꽤 있을 거야.
It-it would mean a lot
if you could be there.
What is wrong with you?
대체 뭘 한 거야?
단 5분도 혼자 놔두질 못하겠군.
Can't leave you alone
for five minutes.
뭔가요, 보스?
What you got, boss?
청첩장.
It is a wedding invitation.
힘드시겠네요.
That's a rough one.
계세요? 아무도 안 계세요?
Hello? Anyone home?
뒷문은 잠겼어.
Back door is locked.
건물 관리인에게 들렀더니,
Building manager came by.
최근에 세든 사람이 자물쇠를 바꿨다더군요.
Said that the tenant
recently changed the locks,
하지만 우리는 이런 거 쉽게 열죠.
but we were free
to pick it.
NCIS!
McGEE:
확실히 H&R블록(유명한 기업명)은 아니군요.
Not exactly H&R Block.
관리인이 다른 말은 안 하던가?
Manager say anything else?
빌린 사람이 현금으로 계산했다고 하더군요.
McGEE: Said the guy that rented
the place paid in cash.
서류를 보여줬는데, 어, 이름은 가짜 같더라구요.
Gave me a description and, uh,
what sounded like a fake name.
뭐, 확실히 누구든 이런 장소를 빌릴 땐 자기 프라이버시를 지키고 싶겠네요.
Well, whoever rented this place
definitely wanted their privacy.
얘기가 나왔으니 말입니다만,
Speaking of which,
어, 보스와 레베카가 있는 방에 허락 없이 들어가서 죄송합니다, 보스.
uh, sorry I walked in
on you and Rebecca, boss.
결혼식에는 가실 거에요?
You going to the wedding?
아니.
No.
이해해요.
Don't blame you.
그녀와 결혼할 남자는, 어, 분명히 보스를 초대한 걸 싫어할 겁니다.
I'm sure the guy she's, uh,
marrying isn't too happy
you were even invited.
더욱이 보스랑 둘이서 그런 걸 알면 더...
Even less so if he found out
that you two...
둘이서 뭐?
You two what?
밤새도록 함께 잔...
Innocently slept
all night long,
하, 하지만, 그러니까, 완전히 잠만 잔거죠?
butt-to-front,
totally innocently?
뭔 말 하고 싶은 거야?
You got something to say?
아뇨! 아뇨, 아닙니다, 아니죠.
No! No, no, no.
저, 저는 빈정댄 게 절대 아닙니다, 보스.
I-I wasn't being sarcastic
at all, boss.
전 단지, 알다시피, 그거 때문에...
I'm just saying
because it, you know...
제가 보기에 두 분이서...
it looked like you two were...
제 말은...
I mean...
저게 뭐죠?
What's that?
뭐, 곤란에 빠진 또 다른 고양이라도 있나, 맥기?
What, another cat
in trouble, McGee?
아뇨, 보스, 보세요.
No. Boss, look.
누군가 여기서 총을 쐈어요.
Somebody fired
a weapon in here.
혈흔이네요.
McGEE:
It's blood.
누군가 닦아내려 했네요, 하지만 확실한 혈흔이 남았네요.
Somebody tried to clean it up,
but it's definitely blood.
차에서 전등을 가져올게요.
I'll get the lights
in the car.
여기서 도대체 뭔 일이 있었던 거죠?
What the hell
happened in here?
좋은 뉴스이야, 나쁜 소식이야?
Heard you have some good
news and some bad news.
사실, 기묘한 뉴스가 있고, 더 기묘한 뉴스가 있지.
Actually, I have weird news,
and I have weirder news.
좋아, 내가 접수할게. 위층에는서 하는 이야기는 전부...
Well, I will take it. All anyone
can talk about upstairs is...
깁스 집에서의 파자마 파티.
The slumber party
at Gibbs' house.
소식 참 빠르지.
News travels fast.
깁스란 사람에 대한 뉴스, 더 빠르지.
Gibbsonian News, even faster.
하지만 난 거기에 참여하지 않을거야.
But I am not gonna
get involved.
흠. 맥기가 그 세금 사무실에서 보내준 DNA 혈흔분석을 했어.
Hmm.
I ran DNA
on the blood samples
that McGee
brought back
from the tax office.
5명의 피해자들이고,
Isolated five victims.
같은 피해자들이야,
They're the same victims
그 식당에서 죽은 사람들 말야.
from the shootout
at the diner.
기묘하네.
That's weird.
내 말이.
Told you.
How did
어떻게 식당의 피해자들이 총격전 현장에 갔을까?
our diner victims
get into a shootout
그 많은 피를 흘리고 나서 마을 한 가운데 있는 거기로 말야.
halfway across town
after losing that much blood?
그들이 간 게 아니야.
They didn't.
내 생각에 식당의 그 현장은 꾸며진 거야.
I think the shootout
at the diner was staged.
피해자들의 손과 옷을 GSR(전기피부반응)로 돌렸더니,
I ran GSR
on the victims' hands
and clothing.
음성 반응이더라고.
It's negative.
그들 중 누구도 총을 쏜 사람은 없다는 거지.
None of them fired
a single bullet.
그렇군.
You're right.
그거 더 기묘해.
That's weirder.
그래. 내 생각에 피해자들은 유인된 거 같아.
Yeah. I think
that the victims were lured
그 세금 사무실로 말야, 그리고 살해됐지.
to the tax office and killed,
그 다음엔 그들의 시체를 식당에 옮긴 거고.
and then, their bodies
were brought to the diner
그리고는 가게에 진열된 마네킹처럼 배치된 거지.
and set up like-like mannequins
in a store display.
그런 짓을 왜 했을까?
Why would anyone do that?
몰라. 난 그저 깁스가 무슨 생각을 했는지 알아내려고 하는 중이야.
No idea. I'm still trying to
figure what Gibbs is thinking,
전부인과 성관계라니, 내 말은,
shacking up
with his ex-wife. I mean,
그녀가 약혼한 걸 알지 못했을 거야, 그치?
there's no way that he knew
she was engaged, right?
내 기억에, 넌 거기에 참여하지 않겠다더니.
I thought you weren't
getting involved.
너도 그래?
You bought that?
내 생각엔 성관계는 아닌 거 같아.
I don't think they shacked up.
듣기에, 옷을 입고 있었댔거든.
I heard they still
had their clothes on.
좋아, 내가 들은 거랑 다르네.
Okay, that's not what I heard.
어떻게 들었는데?
내가 듣기에는...
What'd you hear?
I heard...
잠시만.
Hold that thought.
비숍입니다.
Bishop.
네. 네, 바로 가죠.
Okay. Yeah, be right there.
뭔데?
뭐, 사건 하나는 종료되었는데,
What is it?
Well, we haven't finished one case,
또 다른 사건이 이미 있는거지.
and we already have another one.
하지만 가는 길(운전해 가는 중)에 다른 소문도 알려줘.
But give me some gossip
for the road.
해군 원사인 에킴 빈스.
Master Chief Ekim Beanes.
이웃이 길에 쓰러져 있는 걸 발견하고 911에 연락했답니다.
The neighbors saw him lying
on the street; called 911.
구급대원이 노력했지만, 피를 너무 많이 흘린 상태였답니다.
Paramedics tried
to revive him,
but he lost
too much blood.
덕키는 아직 도착하지 않았지만,
Ducky's not here yet,
가슴에 자상 하나가 있어 보입니다.
but it looks like a single
stab wound to the chest.
피가 꽤나 빠르게 흘렀을 것 같구요.
목격자는?
Probably bled out pretty quickly.
Witnesses?
몇몇 이웃들이 다투는 소리를 들은 것 같다고 합니다.
Some of the neighbors thought
they might have heard an argument.
뭔 것 같나, 강도?
What do you think,
a robbery?
확실치 않습니다.
Doesn't appear.
아니잖아요.
맞아, 그건 부인 2번이고.
- No.
- Yeah, that's wife number two.
정말요?
Really?
말했잖아...
이봐!
I'm telling you...
Hey!
할 말 있나?
You got something to say?
아, 백만년 안에는 없습니다.
Uh, not in
a million years.
사실,
Actually,
저는 단지 제가 보스를 완전하게 이해한다는 걸 아셨으면 합니다.
I just want you to know
I understand completely.
제가 말이죠. 금단의 열매보다 더 끌리는 건 없죠.
I do.
There's nothing
more enticing
than forbidden fruit,
특히 떠 먹을 수 있는 종류는 말이죠.
especially the kind
you can spoon with.
그건...
That was...
아닙니다, 그건 말하면 안되죠.
I didn't...
I shouldn't have said that.
해선 안 될 소리죠.
That's a bad mouth.
맥기...
McGee...
보스, 전 아무 얘기도 안 했습니다.
Boss, I did not
say anything.
저, 저는 모두가 어떻게 아는 건지 모르겠습니다.
I-I don't know how everyone
seems to know.
뭘 알아?
Know what?
알 뭐라도 있다고 그러냐고, 그런 게 있긴 해?
There is nothing to
know. You got that?
맞습니다.
McGEE:
Got it.
어, 깁스?
Uh, Gibbs?
뭐?
What?
피해자 주머니에서 뭘 찾았어요.
Found something
in the victim's pocket.
보셔야할 것 같네요.
You need to see this.
식당에서 죽은 피해자들과 같은 카드군요.
That's the same card one
of our diner victims had.
범인이 연결되어 있군요.
These murders are connected.
사실, 헨리 8세의 부인들을 다 기억하기는 매우 어렵다네.
In fact, it was so hard
to remember
what happened
to Henry VIII's wives
연상기호처럼 된 아이들마냥 말이야.
that as children
we had a mnemonic.
이혼, 몰락, 죽음.
Divorced, beheaded, died,
이혼, 몰락, 살아남음.
divorced, beheaded, survived.
그렇지. 그리고 제쓰로의 미스터리한 부인이 다시 등장하지.
Yes. And with Jethro's
mystery wife back on the scene,
뭔가 유사한 게 필요해질 게야.
we're gonna need
something similar.
어서 오게, 제쓰로!
Hello, Jethro!
난 자네가 너무 일찍 방문한 거 같아 두렵구만.
I'm afraid your visit
is somewhat premature.
저희가 제대로 끝낸 건 X레이 뿐입니다.
The only thing
we've done so far
is the X rays.
잠시 기다리지.
I just wanted a second look.
Yeah.
이 사건 뭔가 있지요, 그렇죠?
There's something
about this one, isn't there?
왠지 본 적 있는 것 같아요.
It's familiar
somehow.
살해흉기를 보고 나도 그렇게 느꼈다네.
I had the same feeling
when I saw the murder weapon.
살해흉기를 가지고 있어요?
You've got the murder weapon?
아마도요. 구급대원이 막 이걸 놓고 갔어요.
Maybe. Paramedics
just dropped this off.
구급대 수습이 심폐소생술 하는 동안 자기도 모르게 집어 갔었대요.
A trainee accidently grabbed it
during the
resuscitation attempt,
그게 그들이 쓰는 도구같아 보여서 말입니다.
thought it was part
of their field kit.
상처와 일치한다네.
It matches the wound,
베인 부분도, 크기도 모두 맞네.
both in shape
and size.
마이크.
Mike.
마이크 프랭크.
Mike Franks.
그의 경우도 정확히 같은 방식이었지.
He was wounded
in the exact same manner.
비슷한 나이기도 하고.
About the same age, too.
또한, 죽은 후 길 한 복판에 버려졌지.
Also, he was
left to die
in the middle
of the street.
일치하는 게 무척 많군요.
That's a lot of coincidences.
아니, 아니야.
No, it's not.
지미가 제가 말했죠,
Jimmy had told me
익숙한 뭔가가 이 피해자들에게 있는 것 같다고요.
that something
felt familiar
about this victim.
그리고 저도 계속 같은 느낌이 식당의 가짜 총격현장에서 느껴졌어요.
And I've had
the same nagging feeling
about the fake shootout
at the diner.
익숙해 보이죠?
Look familiar?
이건 사건 현장 스케치잖아.
네.
It's our crime scene sketch.
Yes.
하지만 어제 건 아니에요.
But not from yesterday.
이건...
This...
세파드 국장님이 살해당한 식당의 스케치예요.
is from the diner
where Director Shepard
was killed.
이게... 최근 사건의 스케치구요.
This... is our
latest crime sketch.
남성 피해자가 여성 피해자를 둘러싸고 있고,
Our male victims surrounded
our female victim.
그녀는 여기있죠.
She was here.
그녀가 처음 총을 쏘고,
She got off the first shot.
남자 1번은 한 발도 못 쏘죠.
Male number one
never even fired his weapon.
핸노버 대령은 그 후에 총을 맞죠.
Captain Hanover took on
heavy fire after that,
어깨에 한 방, 팔에 한 방.
one to the shoulder,
one to the arm.
그녀는 계속 총을 쏘고,
She kept firing.
남자 2번이 맞죠.
Took out male number two
그리고 남자 3번도.
and male number three.
그 다음엔 그녀가 무릎을 꿇고,
Then she dropped to one knee,
세 방을 더 쏘고, 남자 4번이 맞죠.
fired three more shots,
took out male number four.
그리고 난 후에, 그녀는 피를 너무 많이 흘리죠.
And by then she had lost
too much blood.
그럼, 우연히 일어난 건 확실히 아니군.
Well, that is most certainly
not a coincidence.
누군가 깁스의 과거의 살인사건현장을 재현하고 있어요, 깁스.
Someone is recreating murders
from your past, Gibbs.
왜지?
Why?
5구의 시체가 있었고, 총격현장으로 꾸몄습니다.
Five bodies turn up,
staged to mirror the gunfight
켈리포니아에서 있었던 세파드 국장님 사건처럼요.
that killed Director Shepard
in California.
그리고 또 다른 시체가 나타났는데,
Then another
body appears,
이번에는 마이크 프랭크의 살해사건처럼 꾸몄죠.
this time mirroring
Mike Franks' murder.
둘 모두 NCIS였네요.
Both were NCIS.
두 사건 모두 보스와 밀접한 사건이었구요.
Both pivotal figures
in your life.
누군가가 노리고 있어요, 보스.
Somebody's gaslighting you,
boss.
그런가?
You think?
난 이유를 알고 싶군.
I want to know why.
어, 아직 제대로된 이론은 없지만, 의심가는 건 있습니다.
Uh, no theories yet but we
have a few angles on suspects.
세파드 국장님의 살인사건 기록은 봉인되어 있었습니다.
The record from Director
Shepard's murder was sealed.
세부사항을 아는 건 극히 일부 사람들 뿐이죠.
Only a small group of
people had the details.
그리고 우린 서로에 대해 대화를 나눠볼까 합니다.
And we will talk
to each one of them.
그리고...
And then there's...
그리고, 뭐?
Then there's what?
뭐?
What?
이 사건들은 보스와 매우 사적인 관계가 있어요.
These murders
are all very personal to you
그리고...
and...
발생했죠, 그 누군가가 나타나면서요...
occurred when someone else...
매우 개인적으로요.
personal showed up.
보스의 전부인요.
레베카 말인가?
Your ex-wife.
Rebecca?
네.
Yeah.
레베카와는 무관해.
Rebecca isn't involved.
보스, 인정하셔야 합니다,
McGEE:
Boss, you got to admit,
타이밍이 너무 딱 맞아요.
the timing's kind
of interesting.
이봐, 이봐, 이봐.
Look, look, look.
그녀가 완전 제멋대로이긴 해.
She is totally unstable,
완전 엉망이지...
completely
disrespectful...
...신용도 없고... 거짓말쟁이고.
...untrustworthy-- she's a liar.
하지만 살인마는 아니야..
But she's no killer.
보여드려.
Show him.
3개월 전, 엄청난 금액이 그녀의 계좌로 입금됐습니다.
McGEE: Three months ago,
a large deposit was made
to her savings account
from an offshore bank.
수십만 달러였죠.
Hundreds of thousands
of dollars.
지금 이야기하는 여자는 식기세척기 사용법도 제대로 모르는 여자야.
You are talking
about a woman
who doesn't know
how to run a dishwasher.
보여드려요.
Show him.
저는 IRS를 해킹했을 때 사용한 IP주소를 추적했습니다.
I tracerouted the IP address
that was used to hack the IRS.
보스, 레베카가 연루되어 있습니다.
Boss, it belongs to Rebecca.
저희도 그녀가 주동자라고는 생각 않습니다.
We aren't saying
she's the mastermind,
하지만 연관은 되어 있습니다.
but she's involved.
아, 제길.
Oh, man.
나 정말 안 좋은 시기에 커피 마시는 걸 멈췄군.
I picked a really bad time
to stop drinking coffee.
당신도 알죠, 이건 앙갚음이에요.
You know,
this is harassment.
제 약혼자는 변호사예요.
My fianc챕's a lawyer.
당신들이 내셔널 몰의 화장실을 닦는 동안 제 약혼자가 당신들을 끝내버릴 거예요.
삽질하는 동안, 약혼자가 해결할 거란 얘기죠.
You're gonna be scrubbing
toilets at the National Mall
when he gets through
with you.
그리고 그 다음엔...
And then...
내 차례예요.
it's my turn.
당신 변한 게 없네요, 그쵸?
You never change,
do you?
앉아.
Sit down.
제발.
Please.
뭐, 내 인생 최고로 서투른 운행이었어.
Well, that was the most awkward
car ride of my life.
밀크 두드가 필요해.
밀크 두드(milk dud)가 뭔지 잘 모르겠습니다. 상황상 지미가 먹고 있던 과자일까요?
I need a Milk Dud.
그날 밤만으로는 부족했나보지, 허?
Guess you didn't get enough
the other night, huh?
오, 이런.
Oh, snap.
이건 정말 아닌 것 같은데요.
This feels
really wrong.
언제든 나가도 되네.
You can always leave.
농담하세요?
You joking?
늦어서 미안합니다.
Sorry I'm late.
한 마디도 하지마.
Don't say another word. M...
제쓰로.
Jethro.
오랜만이군.
Been a long time.
이 작자는 왜?
What's he doing here?
내 변호사야.
He's my lawyer.
뭐, 내 약혼자가 내 변호사면 안 돼?
What, my fianc챕
can't be my lawyer?
둘이 결혼한다고?
You two are getting married?
청첩장 읽어보지도 않았어?
Did you even read
the invitation?
청첩장?
Invitation?
당신 이 사람을 결혼식에 초대했어?
You invited him
to our wedding?
얘기했잖아요.
We talked about this.
그래, 하지만 난 정말 그럴 줄은 몰랐지.
Yeah, but I didn't think you'd
actually go through with it.
자네에게 뭐라고 하는 건 아니네.
Not that I have anything
against you.
나는 말야... 내 말은...
I'm the one who...
I mean...
몰랐어.
I didn't know.
내, 내가 말했듯이,
I-I told you,
나, 난 그녀가 기혼이란 걸 몰랐다고.
I-I had no idea
she was married.
기가 막히군... 저 사람이 그 사람이야.
레베카가 바람 피우다 제쓰로에게 걸린 그 사람 말이죠.
Shut the front door--
it's him.
나, 난 정말 몰랐다고.
I-I really didn't know.
자네가 원한다면 진술서라도 쓰겠네.
I will even sign
an affidavit if you'd like.
저, 그러니까...
The... I mean...
나, 난 몰랐다고.
I-I didn't know.
커피 금지는 물 건너 가는군.
There goes
the coffee restriction.
내 고객에 대해 뭘 말하길 원하나는 건가?
What do you want to talk
to my client about?
300,000달러.
$300,000.
오프쇼어 은행.
From an offshore bank.
아무 대답 하지 마.
Don't answer that.
좋아, 다른 걸 좀 더 해보지.
Okay, let's try
something else.
이틀 전 밤에 둘 어디에 있었나?
Where were you
two nights ago?
집에 있었나?
Were you at home?
아니면 다른 장소에서 잤나?
Or did you sleep
someplace else?
우연히.
By chance.
그는 낚시질하는 거야.
He's fishing.
그래, 내가 뭘 낚는지 보면서 기다리라고.
Yeah, wait until you
see what I catch.
멜 삼촌이 죽었어.
Uncle Mel died.
아, 지니, 그만.
Ah...
Gene, stop.
그분이 내게 돈을 남겼고, 그분 유언장을 보여줄 수도 있어.
He left me the money, I
can show you the will.
그런거야?
Is that it?
오.
Oh.
누군가...
세상에...
Someone...
God.
이들의 국세청(IRS) 내역을 해킹했어.
hacked their
IRS accounts.
우린 그걸 추적하다 당신에게 이르렀지.
We traced it
back to you.
내가 국세청(IRS)을 해킹했다고 생각해?
You think
I hacked the IRS?
내가?
Me?
무슨 말도 안되는 소리야?
Have you chipped
your sander?
누군가를 돈 주고 고용할 수는 있었겠지.
You could have
paid someone.
당신이 내 앞에 나타난 일부터 이 일들이 시작됐어.
This all started the
day you showed up.
오, 규칙 39번.
Oh, rule 39.
우연한 일 따위는 없다, 맞지?
There's no such thing
as coincidences, right?
그렇지.
That's right.
첫째, 내가 그 규칙을 당신에게 알려줬어.
First of all,
I gave you that rule.
아냐, 당신이 아냐.
아니, 내가 했어.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
그리고 둘째, 당신 머릴 좀 굴려봐, 제이.
And second of all,
use your head, J.
나는 확실히 여기에 있잖아.
I'm clearly being
set up here.
명백히, 누구든 내가 당신을 보러 오는 걸 알겠지.
Obviously, someone knew
that I was coming to see you.
당신이 불러서 온 거지, 나 스스로 온 게 아냐.
That's your lead,
not me.
잠시, 이것 좀 봐.
Well, look at that.
이게 정교한 건 않지만...
It's not sophisticated,
그녀 말이 옳았어.
but she was right.
누군가 레베카가 깁스를 보러 올 거란 걸 알고 있었네.
Somebody did know that
Rebecca was going to see Gibbs.
그녀의 핸드폰이 도청되고 있었어.
Her cell phone
is bugged.
그녀와 다이엔은 깁스 일에 대해 서로 문자를 했었어.
She and Diane have been texting
about Gibbs for weeks.
그 도청 추적 가능해?
Can you trace the bug?
이게 꽤 드문 도청장치더라고.
It's pretty unique.
그래서 내가 FBI의 ViCap데이터베이스를 열어서
So I uploaded
the schematics
into the FBI's ViCAP database
다른 범죄에 이런 게 쓰였나 확인 중이야.
근데 아직은 없어.
to see if it had been used
in other crimes. No hits, yet.
다이엔에게 보낸 문자 내용 좀 보여줘.
I'm gonna need to see
the texts to Diane.
그럴 수는 없지.
: That is
so not happening.
이건 업무상의 일이야, 앱스.
It's for work, Abbs.
좀 해줘 봐.
Come on.
너도 알고 싶잖아,
You know you want
to understand
왜 부인 1번과 2번이 갑자기 난데없이 나타났는지 말야.
why wife number two would just
suddenly appear out of the blue.
난 이미 아는데.
I already know.
그리고 넌 정말로 그걸 알길 원하지 않을거야.
And you really
don't want to know.
왜 아니란 거야?
Why not?
왜냐하면... 이건 슬프거든.
Because... it's sad.
오, 아냐. 어떤 종류에 슬픈 거길래?
Oh, no.
What kind of sad?
너랑 관계 없을 '슬픈 거'.
None of your business
kind of sad.
뭐, 난 이미 레베카가 깁스와 결혼 중에 바람 피운 걸 알고 있어.
Well, I already know
that Rebecca cheated on Gibbs
when they were married.
또한 그녀가 그 바람 피웠던 남자와 결혼하려고 하는 것도 알고 있지.
I also know that she's marrying
the guy she cheated with.
오우.
Oh.
네가 아는 거 전부 말했구나.
You just told me
everything.
고마워, 앱스.
Thank you, Abbs.
난 안 했어.
I did not.
레베카는 관계를 회복하고 싶어했지.
Rebecca wants
to make amends.
깁스가 자신의 결혼을 인정해주는 것으로 말야.
She's here to get
Gibbs' approval for her wedding.
대체 어떻게 그걸 다 안 거야?
How on earth did
you know that?
난 숙련된 조사관이니까.
I'm a trained
investigator.
더하자면, 솔직히 말해서, 모두들 깁스가 그 결혼을 인정하길 원하고 있지.
Plus, let's be honest,
everyone wants Gibbs' approval.
도청장치 찾았다.
I got a hit on the bug.
좋아, 이건 어디에 사용된 건가 하면,
Okay, so it was used
2년 전 미해결 간첩사건에서 사용되었었네.
in an unsolved espionage case
two years ago.
인터폴이 이 사람을 찾고 있고.
Interpol is looking
at this guy.
가에나 율레나.
Ghenna Ulanov.
러시아 사업가지만,
He's a Russian mercenary
지난 해에는 미국 국적을 얻었군.
but has had a U.S. address
for the past year.
들어본 적 없는 사람이야.
Never heard of him.
오, 맙소사.
Oh, no.
이 사람, 세르게이 미셰네브와 일했던 것 같아.
Looks like he's worked
with Sergei Mishnev.
Most Wanted Wall의 제1순위.
"Most Wnated Wal)": NCIS사무실 한쪽 벽에 최우선 수배자들 초상을 붙여둔 벽
Number One with a bullet
on our Most Wanted Wall.
그리고 깁스 집 지하실 벽에도 붙어 있는 녀석.
And Gibbs' personal
basement wall.
뭐, 난 규칙 39번을 별로 쓰고 싶지 않지만,
Well, I hate
to quote rule 39,
확실히 우연은 없는 거로군.
but that is definitely
not a coincidence.
여긴 도저히 누군가 살 것 같지 않네요, 보스.
McGEE: Doesn't look like
anyone's home, boss.
세르게이는 엄청난 문제를 일으킬 겁니다.
Sergei's going to an
awful lot of trouble.
이번엔 어떤 놀이를 하려는 건지 궁급하군요.
I wonder what kind
of game he's playing.
들어갑니다.
McGEE:
Moving in.
좋아, 가지.
All right, let's go.
NCIS.
달아날 구멍은 없는 것 같네요.
No way he jumped out
any windows.
와우.
Whoa.
보스의 전부인이죠?
Is that your ex-wife?
그녀는 감시당하고 있었던 것처럼 보이네요.
Looks like she's been
under surveillance
몇 주간이나요.
for weeks.
헤이, 나 지금 여기 뭐 하는 중이거든.
Hey, I'm right in the middle
of something here.
나도 어찌 돌아가는지는 알아.
I know what's going on.
뭐?
What?
전화로는 얘기 못해.
Can't talk over the phone.
주소를 문자로 보낼게, 30분 안에 만나.
I'm texting you an address;
meet me in a half hour.
이상, 철의 여인.
Iron Lady(철의 여인)은 다이엔의 별명?
Iron Lady, out.
보스, 그녀는 자신이 국세청(IRS)의 직원이지, CIA가 아니란 걸 깨달아야겠네요.
Boss, she does realize
she's an IRS agent,
not CIA?
맥기, 비숍, 여기 이쪽 부분 뜯어가지.
McGee, Bishop,
tear this place apart.
디노조.
DiNozzo,
레베카를 찾아서,
find Rebecca.
그녀를 안전가옥으로 데려가.
Bring her in for
protective custody.
그리고 말야,
And you know what?
지니도 데려가.
지니는 레베카의 변호사이자 약혼자인 그 통통한 남자 이름입니다. (전 깜빡해서 누군가 한참 헤맸지요.)
Gene, too.
어디 가세요?
Where you going?
마타 하리 만나러.
To talk to Mata Hari.
헤이.
Hey.
왜 이리 오래 걸렸어?
What the hell took you so long?
즐길만한 풍경이 있어서 다행이었지만.
Thank goodness I have
this lovely view to enjoy.
어떻게 되어가는거야?
What's going on?
무슨 말이야?
What do you mean?
당신이 어떻게 되어가는지 안다고 말했잖아.
You said you knew
what was going on.
언제?
When?
다이엔.
Diane.
여기서 우리 뭐하는 건데?
Why are we here?
뭐야, 당신이 말해줘야지.
Well, you tell me.
난 한창 메니큐어 칠하는 중이었다고.
I'm in the middle
of getting a manicure,
그러다 이 이상한 문자를 받았고.
and I get this cryptic text
날 만나자는 당신 문자 말야.
from you to meet you
이런 주차장 옥상에서 말이지.
이리와, 가야해.
up on the top of this parking lot.
Come on, we got to go.
지금 당장 가야해.
왜? 뭔데? 왜?
We got to go right now.
What? Why? Why?
어서, 어서, 어서, 서둘러.
Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
이제 겨우 시작이야, 친구.
Only the beginning, my friend.
2마일 내 범위 모든 도로에 검문 강화해.
Road blocks
at every intersection
in a two-mile radius.
그리고 된다면 공중지원도.
And I want air support
if you got it.
가야해
We got to go.
지금 당장 가야해.
왜? 뭔데? 왜?
We got to go right now. Come on.
Why? Why?
NCIS!
모두 엎드려!
Everybody get down!
FBI와 국토안보부가 비상대기 중이얘요.
FBI and Homeland Security
are on high alert.
여기서 중남부로 빠지는 모든 전철역과 공항의 관리자들에게 연락해.
I want agents at every
train station
and airport from here
to the Atlantic.
알겠습니다.
리온은?
On it.
Where's Leon?
벤스 국장님은 회의에서 비행기로 돌아오시는 중입니다.
Director Vance is flying back
from his conference.
좋아, 내가 해군장관님을 만나지.
Okay, get me SECNAV,
정보국(DNI)도.
get me DNI.
포넬과 에밀리를 찾아, 어딨는지.
Find Fornell and Emily,
wherever they are.
깁스, 유감이에요.
Gibbs, I'm so sorry.
맥기?
McGee?
덕키와 지미가 시신을 가져오고 있습니다.
Ducky and Jimmy are bringing
the body in.
저격수가 있던 곳은?
What about the sniper nest?
토니가 갔습니다. 지금까지는 별 게 없어요.
Tony's on it.
So far, nothing useful,
하지만 저희가 뭔가 찾았습니다.
but we have something.
나가신 후, RV카에서 이걸 찾았습니다.
Found it in the RV
after you left.
숨겨진 렙탑에 연결된 작동 센서였어요.
It's a motion sensor wired
to a hidden laptop.
누군가 들어오면 자동으로 보스에게 전화 걸도록 되어 있었습니다.
It's set to call your cell
when someone entered,
그러면 이 녹음이 들리죠.
then play this recording.
나도 어찌 돌아가는지는 알아.
I know what's going on.
전화로는 얘기 못해.
Can't talk over the phone.
주소를 문자로 보낼게, 30분 안에 만나.
I'm texting you an address;
meet me in a half hour.
이상, 철의 여인.
Iron Lady, out.
음성분석기로 작동되는 겁니다.
Ran it through
voice analysis.
이건 거의 구분하기 힘들지만, 확실히 다이엔은 아니었습니다.
It's a good approximation, but it's not Diane.
I know.
세르게이는 그 RV카를 발견하길 원했던 겁니다, 보스.
Sergei wanted us
to find that RV, boss.
그래, 나도 알아.
Yeah, I know.
막 FBI와 이야기 해봤어요.
Just spoke with the FBI.
포넬은 기밀 브리핑 회의에 참석해 있답니다.
Fornell's in
a classified briefing.
메시지를 남길 수가 없었어요.
I didn't leave a message.
컴퓨터에 뭐 더 남은 거 없었나?
There anything else
on the computer?
네, 녹음된 게 하나 더 있었는데, 이건 보스에게 보낸 거였습니다.
Yeah, one more recording,
and this one's for you.
안녕하신가, 깁스 요원.
Hello, Agent Gibbs.
자넨 참 부수기 어려운 사림이야,
You are a hard nut to crack,
미국인들이 얘기하기 좋아하는 것처럼 말야.
as you Americans like to say.
난 모든 단서들을 자네에게 남겼네.
I left you all the clues.
자넨 정말 그게 서서히 다가온다는 걸 알지 못했을 거야.
You really should've
seen it coming.
제법 따끔할거야.
That has to sting.
자넨 내 가족을 망가뜨렸어.
You mess with my family,
난 자네 가족들을 망가뜨리도록 하지.
I mess with yours.
체크(메이트).
Check,
깁스 요원.
Agent Gibbs.
저흰 그가 언급한 가족이 뭔지 잘 모르겠어요.
We're not sure
what family he's referring to.
저희가 아는 한 그에게는 자식이 없는데 말이죠.
No kids we know of.
그의 아버지는 러시아인이고,
His father's Russian.
인터폴은 어머니는 팔레스타인인으로 생각하고 있습니다.
Interpol thinks
his mother's Palestinian.
그들이 그 파일을 보내주기로 했습니다.
They're sending
over the file.
헌데 그 체크라는게 절 매우 불안하게 하는군요.
But it's the check
that makes me most nervous.
보통 이건 (체스에서) 왕을 노릴 거란 경고잖아요.
Usually it means
a checkmate's coming.
좋아, 셋에.
All right, on three.
하나, 둘...
One, two...
아뇨.
No.
뭐라고?
I beg your pardon?
아뇨, 전...
No. I...
그러고 싶지 않아요.
I don't want to.
뭔가 하지 말았으면 하는 게 있나, 팔머 군?
You don't want to what,
Mr. Palmer?
전 이분의 간 무게가 얼만지 알고 싶지 않아요.
I don't want to know how
much her liver weighs.
그녀의 흉터들을 기록하고 싶지도 않고요.
I don't want to catalog
her scars.
하지만 무엇보다, 또 다른 친구를 헤집어놓고 싶지 않아요.
깁스의 마음에 상처주기 싫단 뜻입니다.
But most of all, I don't want
to cut open another friend.
제 생각엔 그게 제 한계인가봐요.
I think I've had my limit.
난 내 한계에 닿는 순간을 기억하기 싫다네,
I don't remember the moment
when I reached my limit,
하지만 같은 일이 벌어지지 않으려면 기억해야만 하지.
but I do remember
never being the same.
그녀를 보고 싶나?
Would you like to see her?
당신은 결코 날 사랑하지 않았어.
You never loved me.
난 당신을 좋아했었어.
I liked you.
지금도 여전히 그렇고 말야.
I still do.
하지만 당신이 계속 사랑한 단 한 여자는 샤넌이었잖아.
But the only woman
you'll ever love is Shannon.
당신은 나의 샤넌이었어, 리로이.
You were my Shannon, Leroy.
시간을 주지.
I'll give you a moment.
아뇨.
No.
포넬에게 연락은 했나?
Have you told Fornell?
아뇨, 제가 직접 하려고요.
No, I'm gonna do that in person.
전 단지 덕키랑 얘길 나누고 싶어서요.
I just wanted to talk to you.
나랑?
Me?
그 자식은 도대체 무슨 짓을 하는 겁니까, 덕키?
What the hell
is this guy doing, Ducky?
세르게이 미셰네브.
Sergei Mishnev.
그는 다소 섬뜩한 게임을 하는 자처럼 보이는군.
Appears he's playing
a somewhat macabre game.
하지만, 만일 우리의 운이 좋다면,
Though, if we're lucky,
이것이 그의 큰 계획 중 일부분일 거라는 거네.
it may actually be part
of a master plan.
운이 좋아요?
Lucky?
우리가 염려하는 그 계획은, 기회가 있는거지,
A plan we can anticipate,
deal with,
막을 수 있단 말일세. 그렇지.
stop. Yeah.
만일 자넬 죽이는 단순한 계획이었을지라도 말야.
Even if it's just a plan
to kill you.
하지만 난 뭔가 잘못되어가는 것 같아 겁이 나네.
But I fear something worse.
세르게이는 자넬 상처 입히고 싶어해.
Sergei wants to hurt you.
뭔가에 대해 자네를 괴롭히고 싶은 것이 분명해.
It's clear he blames you
for something.
뭔가 그에게 아주 큰 상처를 냈어.
Something that wounded him
to the core.
그리고 지금 이건 그의 복수지.
And now it's payback time.
하지만 자넬 죽이는 것만으로는 부족했던 게지.
But killing you
is inadequate.
그는 자네가 고통받는 걸 보고 싶어하네.
He wants to see you suffer.
그 말은 다음에 또 뭔가 있을 거란 것을 의미한다고 확신하네.
Which means that
all bets are off
on what might come next
또는 누군가를 향해 나타날게야.
or for whom he might come.
깁스?
Gibbs?
애비, 뭐 찾았어?
Abby, you got something?
어떻게 세르게이가 그걸 알아냈는지 알겠어요.
I figured out
how Sergei knew
세퍼드 국장님의 죽음과 관련된 모든 기밀들의 세부사항들을요.
all the classified details
of Director Shepard's death.
I.T. 케빈이 그를 위해 바이러스를 만들었어요.
It was the virus
that I.T. Kevin made for him.
이 바이러스는 컴퓨터 시스템을 마구 헤집어놓지 않아요.
It didn't just wreak havoc
on our computer systems.
그냥 그걸 훔치죠.
It stole from them.
그가 뭘 얻어갔지?
깁스의 개인 파일요.
What'd he get?
Your personnel file.
깁스가 함께 일한 모든 사람들의 기록들 말이죠.
Records on everyone
you've worked with.
아직 그 자료 목록을 분석하고 있어요.
I'm still compiling
a list of the data
그 보냈던...
that was sent to...
천재다!
Stroke of genius!
번쩍!
Lightbulb!
섬광이 제 머릴 스쳤어요.
Lightbulb over the head.
제 생각에, 어떻게 세르게이를 찾아야할지 알 것 같아요.
I think I know
how to find Sergei.
아니면 아마도 우리 모두를 죽이거나요.
Or possibly kill us all.
제가 연락할게요.
I'll let you know.
너 제정신이야?
Are you out of your mind?
세르게이의 바이러스를 풀어놓는다고?
You want to release
Sergei's virus?
나쁜 이같지.
Like a bad itch.
정보를 다 모으면 다시 송출된 곳으로 돌아가려고 할거야.
When it gathers its Intel
and tries to phone home,
우린 세르게이에게 돌아가는 그 녀석을 쫓을 수 있어.
we can trace it back to Sergei.
이론상으로는 말야.
In theory.
지난 번에 무슨 일이 있었었는지 기억 나?
Do you remember what happened
last time?
모든 시스템이 날아갔잖아.
It blew out all of our systems.
모든 전기배선이 과열됐었고, 이 건물을 거의 다 탈 뻔 했다고.
The furnace overheated,
almost burned down the building.
그 실수로부터 충분히 배웠어, 됐어?
I've learned
from my mistakes, okay?
이 바이러스에 대해 계속 연구했었다고.
I've been studying this virus.
내 생각엔 이 걸 무해하게 만들 수 있어.
I think I can defang it
with this.
작동은 할 거야, 하지만 해를 끼치진 못해.
It'll run, but it won't
have any teeth.
그래, 하지만 그걸 퍼뜨려서 무해하게 만드는 거잖아.
Yeah, but you're defanging it
by spreading it out
온 도시의 교통 그리드 컴퓨팅에다가 말야.
over the city's
transportation computing grid.
부하를 다룰 수 있는 충분한 대역폭을 가진 가장 비슷한 시스템이니까.
It's the closest system
with enough bandwidth
to handle the load.
괜찮을 거야.
먼저 검증부터 해야해.
It'll be fine.
We need to test it.
시간이 없잖아.
좋아, 그럼 깁스를 부르자.
We don't have time.
Well, then we should call Gibbs.
지금 막 포넬에게 얘기하러 나가실거야.
He just left to talk to Fornell.
깁스를 혼자 내버려 둬야해.
We need to leave Gibbs alone.
알겠지?
Okay?
이 나쁜 자식을 잡고 싶은거야, 아니야?
Do you want to catch
this bastard or not?
좋아, 해보자.
All right, let's do it.
말해.
Talk to me.
저희가 세르게이에게 미끼를 던졌어요.
We have a lead on Sergei
아마 교통국에서 문제가 좀 있을 거에요.
and possibly some trouble
with the Department
of Transportation.
I.T.케빈의 바이러스를 유도 표지로 썼어요.
McGEE: We used I.T. Kevin's virus
as a homing beacon
그리고 그걸 추적해서 그 도시의 아파트 한 곳을 찾았습니다.
어디야?
then traced it to an apartment in the city.
Where?
다이엔이 죽은 곳 옆 건물입니다.
It's the building
next to where Diane was killed.
아파트 2E.
Apartment 2E.
난 할 말 없어.
I'm not much for words.
대부분 아무말 없이 떠나면 더 나아.
Most things are better
left unsaid.
내가 당신을 구할 수 있었다면 굉장히 더 쉬웠을 거야.
It'd be a lot easier
if I could just pick you up
그리고 우린 달리기 시작하고 멈추지 않았을테지.
and we'd start running
and we'd never stop.
하지만 내가 그러기 전에,
But before I do,
난 당신에게 한가지를 물어보고 싶었어.
I just want to ask you
one thing.
그래, 결혼하자.
옛상처를 건드릴 기회?
Yes, I'll marry you.
An opportunity to twist the knife in?
아니, 그건 너의 특별함이야.
No, that's your specialty.
당신이 나랑 함께 하는 건 날 떠나기 위한 건가?
Your way of getting even with me
for leaving you?
인간 항우울제로 지내는 건 쉬운 일이 아니었어.
It wasn't easy being
a human anti-depressant.
내가 안다고는 생각 못했어? 당신이 나랑 결혼한 게
You didn't think I knew?
You just married me
그저 당신이 샤넌과 함께하기 위해서라는 걸 말야.
to get over Shannon?
그게 내가 원한 전부야.
That's all I ever wanted.
내가 사랑하는 누군가의 옆에서 깨는 거.
To wake up next
to someone I love.
넌 나의 사년이야, 리로이.
You were my Shannon, Leroy.
이리와, 서둘러.
지금 당장 가야해.
Come on, we got to go.
We got to go right now.
왜? 뭔데?
Why? Why?
안녕하신가, 깁스 요원.
Hello, Agent Gibbs.
자넨 내 가족을 망가뜨렸어.
You mess with my family,
난 자네 가족들을 망가뜨리도록 하지.
I mess with yours.
당신에게 상처줄 의도는 아니었어.
I never meant to hurt you.
멋지군, 깁스 요원.
Well done, Agent Gibbs.
자네가 이번 전투에서 이겼을지 몰라도,
You may have won this battle,
난 자넬 확실히...
but I assure you...
체크메이트.
Checkmate.
보스?
Boss?
보스, 제 말 들리세요?
Boss, can you hear me?
세르게이는?
Sergei?
사라졌어요.
He got away.
저흴 기다려줘서 고마워요.
Thanks for waiting for us.
보스, 괜찮으세요?
Boss, you okay?
아니.
No.
저희도요.
Neither are we.
그들에겐 여기저기 미해군 기관들을 들쑤실 수많은 계획들이 있었어요.
They've got blueprints
for dozens
of U.S. military installations
all over the place in there.
그들은 그 계획을 실행하려고 했던 것처럼 보였지만,
It looks like they
tried to take them,
그것들 대부분을 남겨두고 떠났어요.
but they left most
of them behind.
뭐, 그건 좋군. 그 말은 그들이 뭘 계획했건 우리가 그걸 막았단 거잖아.
Well, that's good.
That means whatever
they were planning,
we stopped it.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man